sup everyone cameras on the t45 here
with a very special video today
now something pretty wild after day well
I was on the toilet taking a and I
thought the fish' cannot be happening
but it did and I really how'd
you tell this story yeah well before
start telling the story some of you may
be wondering what's up with a set of
here I feel like I need a background so
I wasn't just pointing in like a wall
wall so I just put up my Sonic on the
ground V's and these two things this is
my this tattoo was like Godlike from the
Chinese right there was this a Chinese
restaurant not too far from where I live
in and there's like this many
Mishima good attitudes and I got these
two which really remind me of Sonic and
Bobby and it was a fake cuz I like and I
put like 50 cents for each of them so I
spent like a doll on this and well
anyways they care like one after each
other they look just like soccer Bobby
you can't tell me that that is not fan
cook black every now and then I
like to act like these tattoos I like
having sex and I was gonna put the
mic right here on my arm just say show
people look at my own ass to put
ball Bardonic but I didn't want to waste a
tattoo so I just I just keep them around
close by like on my bedside drawing
so I can look at every nap and just
think about like how fate gave me these
two things because because they they
like look like bow down and like
Bobby and song and that's not the suit I
wanted to her the suit our hotel is wild
so here's what it is
I just got done having dinner and I went
to my bathroom to take a
like ah I took the biggest dumb be like
it I took a big awesome it was like like
take that but make it three times louder
that was my dumb
was insane and I kid you not while I was
taking that I heard what sounded
like the window in my living room
opening from the outside Kim I know
nothing else my mama she was at the
grocery store some
she wasn't even home so I know that
wasn't her even if it was why would she
be open on my window from the outside
she wouldn't then I heard someone
climbing in and right after that I heard
I kid you not what sounded just like
Jolie awhile I kid you not be just I
swear jaliwa was in my house I
don't know why I don't know what he was
doing here he did still show anything
was just in my half I swear I
heard him talking he wasn't talking in
strong voice anything he was talking in
in his number voice I put had to go
through my living room to check the TV
do you check if he was there you
checking of those like a TV or shower or
something on there was him he was in my
living room I mean what a block
you don't know is javi why is a pretty
close family friend of my family so I
tried calling up saying Julia why were
you in my house he didn't answer back so
I'm the rock then there something was up
that was in my house I mean what
was he doing in my house he's the voice
app for those who don't know Julia why
is the voice actor Assad's Hedgehog like
I I I'm thinking about going over to
file a police report or some
tomorrow morning but I don't know
that's weird as if it wasn't him it
might have been just some backup but
that's even weirder
if it was a noah blacker he would
on something but but this guy didn't
steal although I always mention my
sock Underground DVD was knocked over
and when I came out of the back after
walking my ass I walked it over went
straight to my DVD case because my sock
on DVD on my oh my my sock under
Gandhiji's on my most prized possession
so I went over there check one of the
DVDs was knocked over it was it was like
that it was knocked over Jumby it almost
said the Julia I was like looking
through my DVDs or some